{
    "subject": "resource/Yemen",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Sana'a",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Yemen is Sana'a.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9608353972434998,
            "question": "Is Sana'a a city in Yemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8665145635604858,
            "question": "What is the capital of Yemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8322327136993408,
            "question": "Does Yemen have a capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8063514232635498,
            "question": "What is the name of the capital city of Yemen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7760599851608276,
            "question": "Which country has Sana'a as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5839395523071289,
            "question": "Where is Sana'a located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5433701872825623,
            "question": "Is Sana'a a historical city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29779085516929626,
            "question": "Name the largest city in Yemen."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29503491520881653,
            "question": "What are some important landmarks in Sana'a?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2593046724796295,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Sana'a?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Yemen is Sana'a.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8956_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some important landmarks in Sana'a?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8956_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the largest city in Yemen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8956_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Sana'a a historical city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8956_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8956_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided consistently support that the capital of Yemen is Sana'a, with multiple references to this fact."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}